<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>infographic on Rob likes to code.</title>
    <link>https://petr.in/categories/infographic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in infographic on Rob likes to code.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://petr.in/categories/infographic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Title Tally</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/title-tally/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/title-tally/</guid>
      <description>Title Tally, hosted on Netlify, is near and dear to my heart. I was having a difficult time quantifying which cities had the most collective championships. I could to this per-franchise, but wanted to segment data to differentiate the Minneapolis Lakers from the Los Angeles Lakers, for example.
Originally written in Vue, I&amp;rsquo;ll be working on a React version in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mat Stat</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/mat-stat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/mat-stat/</guid>
      <description>Mat Stat is my most recent sports infographic project, and it is hosted on Netlify.
Like Title Tally, it looks to quantify championship victories using a number of metrics (time, location, etc.). Unlike Title Tally, this time it focuses on major professional wrestling promotions. The front-end is vanilla JavaScript. I haven&amp;rsquo;t decided if the back-end will be dynamic (scraped from Wikipedia) or static (compiled in a local database) yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston: Win City</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/boston-win-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/boston-win-city/</guid>
      <description>A lot has been said about the run of New England sports teams since the turn of the century. While the teams have won many championships, the run of appearances in the final four (Conference/League Final) has been equally unprecedented. This project, a work in progress, looks to quantify that. Check it out on CodePen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
