<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>work-in-progress on rob@petrin.dev</title>
    <link>https://petr.in/categories/work-in-progress/</link>
    <description>Recent content in work-in-progress on rob@petrin.dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://petr.in/categories/work-in-progress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Petrin Development Services</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/petrin-dot-dev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/petrin-dot-dev/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m launching Petrin Development Services (PDS) in 2022. The plan is to use my skills, experiences, and expertise to help small businesses in my area to cultivate their marketing presence, and to help them manage all applicable web services that can help them grow their brand.
In the last few years, proper technical SEO hygiene has become more important than ever. And, in my humble opinion, it&amp;rsquo;s becoming too treacherous of a landscape for small business owners to focus on while separately growing their businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston: Win City</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/boston-win-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/boston-win-city/</guid>
      <description>A lot has been said about the run of New England sports teams since the turn of the century. While the teams have won many championships, the run of appearances in the final four (Conference/League Final) has been equally unprecedented. This project, a work in progress, looks to quantify that. Check it out on CodePen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Title Tally</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/title-tally/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/title-tally/</guid>
      <description>Title Tally, hosted on CodePen, is near and dear to my heart. I was having a difficult time quantifying which cities had the most collective championships. I could to this per-franchise, but wanted to segment data to differentiate the Minneapolis Lakers from the Los Angeles Lakers, for example.
Originally written in Vue, I&amp;rsquo;ll be working on a React version in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mat Stat</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/mat-stat/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/mat-stat/</guid>
      <description>Mat Stat is my most recent sports infographic project, and it is hosted on CodePen.
Like Title Tally, it looks to quantify championship victories using a number of metrics (time, location, etc.). Unlike Title Tally, this time it focuses on major professional wrestling promotions. The front-end is vanilla JavaScript. I haven&amp;rsquo;t decided if the back-end will be dynamic (scraped from Wikipedia) or static (compiled in a local database) yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subject Matter Experts</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/subject-matter-experts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/subject-matter-experts/</guid>
      <description>Subject Matter Experts (SME) is perhaps the most important project listed here, and closest to my heart. I have a vision for re-imagining self-directed education, with a &amp;ldquo;lesson&amp;rdquo; as the primary increment for measuring understanding. Any subject can be broken down into the lessons it consists of, and I believe an entire educational platform (or a curriculum, or a doctrine) can be formatted comprised of lessons.
SME looks to implement that vision, as five primary applications &amp;ndash; a lesson composer, a lesson repository, an assessment tool, a student dashboard, and a curriculum dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Holdem</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/texas-holdem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/texas-holdem/</guid>
      <description>This a simple proof-of-concept for now, with limited functionality. It&amp;rsquo;s not actively being worked on, but can be found on CodePen. It deals cards correctly, but none of the underly game functionality is present yet. It uses the Deck of Cards API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Means War!</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/this-means-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/this-means-war/</guid>
      <description>This a simple proof-of-concept for now, with limited functionality. It&amp;rsquo;s not actively being worked on, but can be found on CodePen. It deals cards correctly, but none of the underly game functionality is present yet. It uses the Deck of Cards API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabric.js Drawing Tool</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/fabric-js-draw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/fabric-js-draw/</guid>
      <description>This tool, first developed in 2018, is a proof of concept for a pictionary app I&amp;rsquo;d like to further develop. It is fully featured, but lacks any current practical application. The tool is currently hosted on CodePen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
