<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rob likes to code.</title>
    <link>https://petr.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rob likes to code.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://petr.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Bengals Will Win</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/blog/bengals-will-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/blog/bengals-will-win/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I really want the Bengals to win, and I expect they will.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January is Nerd Season</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/blog/january-is-nerd-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/blog/january-is-nerd-season/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As noted in my prior post, I expected a busy time in January. It hasn&amp;rsquo;t disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022 Will Feel Like Mach Speed</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/blog/2022-at-mach-speed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/blog/2022-at-mach-speed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I expect this year to be a whirlwind, which is saying something compared to the prior few years.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petrin Development Services</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/petrin-dot-dev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/petrin-dot-dev/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m launching Petrin Development Services (PDS) in 2022. The plan is to use my skills, experiences, and expertise to help small businesses in my area to cultivate their marketing presence, and to help them manage all applicable web services that can help them grow their brand.
In the last few years, proper technical SEO hygiene has become more important than ever. And, in my humble opinion, it&amp;rsquo;s becoming too treacherous of a landscape for small business owners to focus on while separately growing their businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston: Win City</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/boston-win-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/boston-win-city/</guid>
      <description>A lot has been said about the run of New England sports teams since the turn of the century. While the teams have won many championships, the run of appearances in the final four (Conference/League Final) has been equally unprecedented. This project, a work in progress, looks to quantify that. Check it out on CodePen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Title Tally</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/title-tally/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/title-tally/</guid>
      <description>Title Tally, hosted on CodePen, is near and dear to my heart. I was having a difficult time quantifying which cities had the most collective championships. I could to this per-franchise, but wanted to segment data to differentiate the Minneapolis Lakers from the Los Angeles Lakers, for example.
Originally written in Vue, I&amp;rsquo;ll be working on a React version in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mat Stat</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/mat-stat/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/mat-stat/</guid>
      <description>Mat Stat is my most recent sports infographic project, and it is hosted on CodePen.
Like Title Tally, it looks to quantify championship victories using a number of metrics (time, location, etc.). Unlike Title Tally, this time it focuses on major professional wrestling promotions. The front-end is vanilla JavaScript. I haven&amp;rsquo;t decided if the back-end will be dynamic (scraped from Wikipedia) or static (compiled in a local database) yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subject Matter Experts</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/subject-matter-experts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/subject-matter-experts/</guid>
      <description>Subject Matter Experts (SME) is perhaps the most important project listed here, and closest to my heart. I have a vision for re-imagining self-directed education, with a &amp;ldquo;lesson&amp;rdquo; as the primary increment for measuring understanding. Any subject can be broken down into the lessons it consists of, and I believe an entire educational platform (or a curriculum, or a doctrine) can be formatted comprised of lessons.
SME looks to implement that vision, as five primary applications &amp;ndash; a lesson composer, a lesson repository, an assessment tool, a student dashboard, and a curriculum dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sentify</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/sentify/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/sentify/</guid>
      <description>I worked on the current iteration of the Sentify website in early 2020. This was strictly a development engagement, as a number of their services overlap with what I offer as part of Petrin Development Services. But it was a fun little website I enjoyed contributing to, and perhaps may continue to contribute to in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Holdem</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/texas-holdem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/texas-holdem/</guid>
      <description>This a simple proof-of-concept for now, with limited functionality. It&amp;rsquo;s not actively being worked on, but can be found on CodePen. It deals cards correctly, but none of the underly game functionality is present yet. It uses the Deck of Cards API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trivia Blitz</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/trivia-blitz/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/trivia-blitz/</guid>
      <description>This game is fully-functioning, and is hosted on CodePen. It uses the Open Trivia Database, which is a super easy API to work with, but the difficulty settings are a little wacky. Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock, Paper, Scissors Simulator</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/rps-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/rps-simulator/</guid>
      <description>This is a dumb little game I created in a couple of hours. Hosted on CodePen, it is exactly what you would expect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dice Rolling Game</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/dice-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/dice-game/</guid>
      <description>This game can be found on CodePen, and is based on a mini-game from the Jackbox Party Pack game Trivia Murder Party. Each player takes turns rolling. The first player to get to 21 wins!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tic Tac Toe</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/tic-tac-toe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/tic-tac-toe/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s not much to see here. This little app, hosted on CodePen, is a fully-functioning Tic Tac Toe game. It can be played alone (but why?) or with a friend. A left-click (or tap) is X, and a right-click (or long tap) is O.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Means War!</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/this-means-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/this-means-war/</guid>
      <description>This a simple proof-of-concept for now, with limited functionality. It&amp;rsquo;s not actively being worked on, but can be found on CodePen. It deals cards correctly, but none of the underly game functionality is present yet. It uses the Deck of Cards API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabric.js Drawing Tool</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/fabric-js-draw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/fabric-js-draw/</guid>
      <description>This tool, first developed in 2018, is a proof of concept for a pictionary app I&amp;rsquo;d like to further develop. It is fully featured, but lacks any current practical application. The tool is currently hosted on CodePen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Water Coolest</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/the-water-coolest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/the-water-coolest/</guid>
      <description>I had a lot of fun working on The Water Coolest. I first joined them as a the voice of their daily news podcast, which leaned on my recording and audio production skills. Additionally, I took on duties related to landing page development, and broader management of their entire marketing site. Subsequently, they were acquired by Barstool Sports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homebody Media</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/homebody-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/homebody-media/</guid>
      <description>Homebody Media was a labor of love, as a number of colleagues were looking to develop a podcasting network. Built in Hugo, the requirements for integrating the site were both to foster content management and proper podcast RSS feed syntax. The theme was fully custom, and a joy to develop. HBM is currently on hiatus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn More Details About Rob Petrin</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:05:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/about/</guid>
      <description>Rob was born in 1986, and is originally from Rhode Island. He likes coding, camping, civics, politics, podcasting, and professional wrestling. In his spare time, he plays video games, spends time with his family, and dreams of retiring to Vermont.
Professional Lead Front-End Developer, Astute Communications (2022 - Present)
As Lead Front-End Developer, I work closely with the Design department to translate their work into living-and-breathing code for our clients. I manage the entire front-end process for our team, and have a great deal of autonomy into the tooling used to get the job done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Association of School Librarians</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/vaasl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/vaasl/</guid>
      <description>My work on the VAASL website was challenging. There were rigid design requirements within their existing design system, as the site was a pioneer in accessibility. This hindered innovation, but resulted in a clean site &amp;ndash; though admittedly the theme we were working in was very dated (even for 2015). The site has had a subsequent redesign in the intervening years, after my involvement ended.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Mary&#39;s Jr/Sr High School</title>
      <link>https://petr.in/portfolio/st-marys/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://petr.in/portfolio/st-marys/</guid>
      <description>Unfortunately, St. Mary&amp;rsquo;s is now closed. I took over development of the site in 2014, which badly needed a re-theme. It is based on WordPress, and uses a boilerplate theme. This project was more of an exercise in content than functionality, as the site&amp;rsquo;s primary purpose was transmitting information.
This was one of my earlier forays into graphic design, as I implemented the global hero banner, and the Crimson Eagle logo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
